For the Man Who Has Everything
Perfect Gift is a comedy film directed by Michael Paul Girard.
An erotic comedy about a man who meets a sensuous, fun-loving girl at a
pajama party after separating from his dour girlfriend.
His new love searches high and low to find someone to
fulfill his ultimate fantasy - a menage a trois.
Randal, played by John McCafferty.
Suzanne, played by Kim Dawson.
Carol, played by Ashlie Rhey.
Lori, played by Monique Parent.
Sheffield, played by Nicholas Ball.
Ted, played by Al Sapienza.
Picture Perfect is a 1997 American romantic comedy film directed by Glenn Gordon Caron, written by Arleen Sorkin, and
starring Jennifer Aniston, Jay Mohr, Kevin Bacon, Illeana Douglas, Olympia Dukakis, and Anne Twomey.
The film centers around a young advertising executive's life, which becomes increasingly complicated
when, in order to impress her boss, she pretends to be engaged to a man she just met.
Picture Perfect was released on August 1, 1997, by 20th Century Fox.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $44.3
million against an $18 million budget.
The tone is lighthearted.